in the RP sector there is a massive gap
of getting experienced ARP Consultants
especially when we look in the Dynamics
field and around business Central so
Partners which face Talent Gap
challenges now have the option to join
the program our reskilling program we
recruit individuals which come out of
the industry and we reskilled them we
retrain them to become business cental
professionals Consultants or developers
this is finally what we've been looking
for a way where Microsoft as the
publisher was partnering with us to try
to find that next Generation talent pool
that we really need to bring into the
[Music]
ecosystem so this Talent program has
actually allowed me to fulfill a dream
which I've had of working in technology
within construction for a very long time
I was actually lucky that the talent
program contacted me and have supported
me right through from day one to get to
where I wanted to be I was not sure how
my set of skills could mix well together
for a proper career path and then I
realized that being a Microsoft business
Central consultant could be the perfect
answer that I was looking for clients
first really allows me to be creative in
my Learning Journey it's really
refreshing to have such a guided program
you don't feel alone in it and you're
with the community the thing I like
about the Microsoft Talent program is uh
the mix of the theory and the practice
and that's just a perfect way for me to
Res skill myself what I appreciate the
most at trimit is they are appreciating
me as a person and they trust my uh
ability I hope that I'm not only a
consultant 5 years from now but also 25
years from now oh
yeah so for partners are considering
joining the Microsoft Talent program I
would really recommend that it's a great
way of growing new skill sets within
your business and that is what is is
going to drive the future of your
business so get on board
now